What's going on?
Well, uh, I think that bamboo tree was possessed.
This can't be good.
We are the notorious Foxy Pirates!
We want more than just a fight from you.
We want a showdown!
A Davey back with the Foxy Pirates!
I'm in your debt.
Come to my house and let me show you some hospitality.
Awesome! I'm starving!
Me too!
Finally home after all these years.
It's a custom in this village to treat visitors
to extra delicious milk from our extra long farm animals.
Village? I didn't see any village out there.
Or a farmhouse.
Now that you mention it...
The whole village is gone!
All our animals, too!
You're nuts, old man.
I know it's been ten years,
but whole villages don't just disappear.
Yes, but this is a special case.
I'll save the explanation
until after we've had a nice cool drink.
I believe I've had some milk tucked away somewhere.
Hmm.
Did you say milk?
You realize you were stuck on those stilts for ten years, right?
I hope this cheese is to your liking.
You think we're stupid?
You can't pass off your disgusting old milk as cheese!
If you don't want to eat it, I won't force you.
But far be it from me till the cheese go to waste.
Wait, so you're saying it's okay to eat this stuff after all?
Are you out of your mind?
What's the big deal?
Some cheese tastes better once it's finally aged.
Your high-stress lifestyles have made your stomachs weak,
whereas laid-back fellows such as myself
can eat whatever we like.
You kids go on your fancy adventures,
but you're shy when it comes to new food.
Someone call the doctor.
What did you think was going to happen?
Moron!
Doctor, someone's getting a doctor!
Hurry!
Wait, that's me!
It's food poisoning.
Yeah, you think?
You're funny, old man.
You okay?
Yes, excluding the fact that the entire camp
packed up and moved on without me.
I see now.
The village didn't disappear, it moved.
That must mean the people here are nomads.
Indeed, and Long Ring Long Land Island is our home.
You are welcome here.
Oh, thanks.
The island got its name from its ring-like shape.
Although it's technically one big circle,
the tide's divided into ten smaller islands.
You probably wouldn't guess that all of the islands
were actually connected,
but once a year, when the tides are at their lowest,
you can see Long Ring's true form,
if only for a few hours.
We use this time to migrate from one island to the next
every three years,
circling the ring again and again.
Oh.
So everyone moved to the next island
while you were stuck up in the trees.
But rotten luck.
That's a good one.
You're a real rebel, old man.
If they stay on each island for three years,
then subtracting the ten years you spent living
on those stupid bamboo stilts,
it would still take a good 20 years
for them to come back around and meet up with you again.
Assuming you don't eat that cheese of yours
and die of food poisoning, of course.
Well, it's sad but true.
I just wish I had my
to ride again.
Then I could cross an island
every time the tides were low
and catch up to the other villages
in only five years.
That's right.
They're the most graceful and beautiful animals
on the whole island.
Once tame, they can be used to cross the grassy plains
with the greatest of ease.
Without them, it would be impossible
for our people to migrate.
After all, our belongings are far too heavy
to carry on our own.
And even if we were strong enough
to move all our luggage,
the tide would still rise and drown us
before we could make it across.
Wouldn't it be easier to take a boat instead?
Yes, of course, but unfortunately,
we don't know how to sail.
And besides, even if we were able
to charge a log post here,
that doesn't mean it would point to the next island.
The land may be split into ten pieces,
but it's all part of the same place.
Suppose I'll just have to wait 20 years.
You'll be lonely.
That's a long time.
Oh, wait a second.
Is a horse like a horse?
Hey, I almost forgot about that.
We saw a horse on the way here.
Huh?
Oh, my sweet little Shelly,
you waited for me all these years.
You're such a pretty girl.
Look at you.
So cute.
I missed you so much.
You sure grown long since I've been away.
Oh, you make me so proud.
Good girl.
That's a good girl.
I'm so sorry if you were lonely while I was gone.
It's all my fault.
I promise I'll never leave you again.
Don't leave her waiting.
She wants to go for a ride.
What a pow, huh?
Even though everyone else left,
she's still hung around all these years.
That's my kind of horse.
I don't know which one of them is happier right now.
Man, that horse sure is fast, huh?
I want to ride it, too.
I see why that old man likes horses so much.
Now that I'm back, let's cross the sea together
as soon as the tide is low again, okay?
You've waited through rainy days
and you've waited through snowy days as well.
But from now on, we'll have nothing but sunshine.
Shelly, are you sure you won't wait here
for Tonjit all alone?
We're taking all your friends with us.
Please, Tonto, wait, come back!
Please, come with us, Shelly.
We won't return to this island for 27 years.
You're going to be lonely
if you have to stay here all by yourself.
We don't know where Tonjit ran off to.
It's not worth waiting here.
He might be gone for good.
I'm going to stay here, too.
Grandpa's coming back.
I just know it.
Don't be foolish.
Let me down.
I'm not going to leave Shelly and Grandpa all alone.
Stop.
Let me go.
Grandpa's coming back.
I know it.
We have to wait for him.
Good luck, old girl.
Live well.
Shelly!
We have to wait for it.
You know this old man's afraid of heights, don't you?
Oh, no!
Are you okay?
Huh?
Shelly!
What happened?
We heard a gunshot!
Ooh, this head!
Here, I'll get it!
Sorry, suckers, but that horse is mine!
Yeah, you tell them, boss.
Put those losers in their place.
Whoever you are, you'll pay!
Whoever you are, you don't know?
My goodness!
How rude!
P-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p.
Don't tell me you've never seen this face before!
The only thing I know about your face is that I'm gonna break it!
He really doesn't know me!
Oh, no, don't get depressed, boss!
He's just saying that!
It's a joke!
Everybody knows who you are!
Don't tell me you've never seen this face before!
The only thing I know about your face is that I'm gonna break it!
He really doesn't know me.
Oh, no, don't get depressed, boss. He's just saying that.
It's a joke. Everybody knows who you are.
Like you'd have any reason to know him.
Boo-boo-boo-boo-boo-boo-boo!
You're gonna make him cry, Hamburg!
My name is Foxy.
What's mine is mine, and what's yours is mine too!
Fifi, you should see the looks on your dumb faces!
What kind of pants he gets so marked up over some stupid horse?
If I didn't steal that thing myself, then somebody else would do it!
That's enough!
Come, come!
Hold it, Luffy, not yet!
How'd you know my name was Luffy?
Because unlike some people, we did our homework.
Monkey D. Luffy with a 100 million berry bounty.
Roro Noah Zoro with a 60 million bounty.
A lump of cash like that is nothing to scoff at,
especially considering that you only have seven crew members.
Now, with introductions out of the way,
as captain of the Foxy Pirates,
I challenge you, Straw Hats, to a Daveyback fight!
I don't know what that means,
but if you want to fight, bring it on!
I'm sick of hearing you talk!
Wait, now it all makes sense.
I bet that messed up crew we saw on the way here
got challenged to a Daveyback fight, too!
Which way do we turn?
Those!
Where's the Navigator?
Give orders!
What, Navigator?
Captain!
The captain!
This is bad.
I've got to stop him.
Luffy, no!
We're going to end up losing our crew!
What are you talking about, Usopp?
I know this guy's a jerk, but you can't agree to fight him!
Hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi!
Fe, fe, fe, fe!
Oh, too bad, kid.
But no take backs!
You already agreed, remember?
Bring it on, I believe you said.
Ain't that right, Porcha?
Oh, that was definitely a bring it on, I heard.
And once you say bring it on, there's no turning back.
That's the rule.
Should've kept your mouth shut.
What's wrong?
Don't tell me you aren't man enough to keep your word.
M2!
You're falling into his trap!
But what about the horse?
Come on!
Shelly, oh.
You landed on your back pretty hard.
Don't push yourself too much.
Both of you step aside.
Are you crazy?
Shelly waited 10 years for me to come back.
I won't let you take her!
I know that you're angry, but those are pirates, old man!
You said the fight's already started?
That's right!
A Davyback fight begins as soon as one captain accepts the challenge from the other captain.
No take backs!
In other words, your captain is fighting our captain whether you like it or not.
All you can do is sit back and deal with it.
I don't get this.
If it's a fight, why do I have to sit and wait?
Let's do this right here, right now.
You don't know anything, do you?
It's not a real fight.
It's more like a sports match between different pirate crews.
Exactly.
Supposedly the game originated in a faraway place called Pirate Island.
As the name implies, it's a sort of secret paradise for pirates.
At any rate, the main purpose of a Davyback fight is to plunder
desirable members from another pirate's crew.
Pirates plundering other pirates?
Yes.
No wonder your puny little crew only has seven members.
A Davyback fight is the best way to pull in some new recruits.
Since you're so clueless, I'll tell you how it works.
After each match, the winner can take any crew member they want from the losing team.
And once that person is chosen, they gotta pledge their undying loyalty to their new captain on the spot.
Both crews take their oath in the name of Davy Jones, the Pirate of the Deep.
So if you lose, you lose a crew member?
Now you're getting it!
Also, if the losing team doesn't have any members worth plundering,
the winning captain can add insult to injury by robbing the ship of its jolly roger.
So you're not just betting your crewmates, but the pride of your ship too.
Winning might make you stronger, but losing can leave you with nothing at all.
Might as well be betting your life.
I see. That explains it. That ship without a captain or a navigator or sail.
They must have lost everything in a Davyback fight.
Oh? So you saw the Fang Frog Pirates, or what's left of them at least?
How about we give you a chance to admire our handiwork in person?
Here! Let's have a round of applause for our brand new recruits!
Long live the Foxy Pirates!
Before I came here, I was the captain of the Fang Frog Pirates!
I was the doctor.
I was the navigator.
And I was the shipwright!
We played five three-coin games and lost them all.
The captain, 13 crew members, and our jolly roger taken away.
With so many people jumping ship, I guess it was more like a merger than anything.
What about your crew, huh? You don't care? Just join a new ship and leave them out to dry?
Yeah, no kidding. Those poor saps got a one-way ticket to a watery grave.
Watery grave? That's their problem. Don't look at me.
You're nothing but scum. We're not playing your stupid game. Got it?
There's no way we'd ever sink to your level.
You can say that all you want, but it ain't the crew's decision to make.
The Davyback fight begins the second one captain agrees to another captain's challenge.
What's the matter? Don't you have faith in your captain?
If you don't agree with the decisions he makes, maybe you're better off joining us after all.
Sorry, Nami, but they're right.
Huh?
All pirates take an unwritten oath to follow their captain to the bitter end.
If we turned our back on this fight now, we'd be sailing away in disgrace.
So? Who cares? That's better than losing.
Maybe for you, but I'd rather die than live in disgrace.
The same goes for me.
Are you kidding? Get over yourself!
You know how men can be. There's no point in arguing with them.
Ugh! I'll stop Luffy by force if I have to!
Don't bother! It's too late.
All that's left now is to sit back and wait for the captains to fire a shot to signal the beginning of the match.
Oh, no way!
Ugh. Guess that settles it.
Well, I'm not complaining.
Should be interesting, at least.
He's agreed to the game!
Yee-haw!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Stupid!
Why didn't you agree? You could end up losing your crew!
You could lose me!
Yee-haw! I'm gonna win this thing!
Now the Daveyback fight is officially underway!
Good! The sooner I can pound your face in, the better!
I'd like to see you try!
All right! Bring it on, split head!
He doesn't like my haircut!
That's not true!
Hey! Apologize to him! Our boss is sensitive about his looks!
He's sensitive about everything! He's got a heart of glass!
How many times do I have to tell you? Don't laugh!
Luffy, now listen, I'm as angry about the old guy's horse as you are, but this is madness!
Good! Use that anger to thrash him!
What are you doing up? I thought you hurt your back!
Leave it to me!
You don't know what you're getting into.
Sausage on the stick! Get your sausage on the stick!
We got rum, we got cheeseburgers, turkey legs, yakisoba, we got it all!
It's time for the opening ceremonies! Everybody, simmer down, simmer down!
You simmer down!
Shut up!
Come on, let's hear the odds!
All competitors get ready!
Split head may be a jerk, but he sure knows how to party!
And check out all the people he invited! Is that his crew?
Wow, there's so many!
Five jumbo yakisobas, please.
Whose side are you on, huh?
Now, let's calm down, boys! We're about to start!
I love you, Portia! Marry me!
Since our challengers have never played this game before, let's go over the rules, okay?
First of all, whatever you lose in one of the matches, whether it's your crew,
your Jolly Roger, or anything else, the only way you can take it back is with another Davey-backed fight!
Second, any crew member taken by the winner must swear undying loyalty to their new captain on the spot, no exceptions!
Third, if your Jolly Roger is taken, you can't ever fly it again, never ever!
Nami! I got you some cotton candy!
I don't know how everyone can be so calm at a time like this!
That's already settled, so you might as well stop complaining.
Finally, if you happen to break any of these rules, you'll be labeled a disgrace to all pirates and
banished to Davey Jones' locker! So do you swear to uphold them?
I swear! I swear!
All right then, Straw Hat, I'll let you choose your fate! One coin, two coins, three coins, it's all up to you, kid!
That's our boss for you! Always a good sport!
What do the coins do?
Decide the number of gains. The boss is letting you choose how many matches you want to have.
You can quit after one, or you can do as many as three if you're feeling lucky.
Well, the more games we do, the more fun we'll have, right? So let's...
Snoopy!
Got it!
Okay, then I'll take three!
You idiot! Why did you add them? And why did you count an enemy, too?
That was easy.
Then it's settled! Three coins, three games, orthodox rules!
Let Davey Jones be our witness!
Huh? So who's this Davey Jones guy?
A pirate who was cursed by the devil and forced to spend all of eternity at the bottom of the sea.
I've never heard of people living underwater.
Well, that's what the legend says. And all the ships and treasures that sink beneath the waves go to his locker.
Never to be seen by anyone again.
I knew the ocean was scary, but that's crazy!
Yummy!
Davey Jones has been taking his picks from all sorts of pirates for as long as anyone can remember.
That's why we call it a Davey-backed fight in honor of the pirate that may someday claim your crew is his own.
The stage of battle is set, sir!
The beats grieve, but the weapon is myöker.
We'll see you next time.
On the next, One Piece, round one, one lap of the doughnut race, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!